About

Systems and Computer Engineer with programming skills, web development, planning and learning capacity, participation with more than 2 years in different projects of the academic direction and Hotbed of Research in Applied Robotics Sirap of the Caldas of University

1.5 years of experience in development and adaptation of learning platforms for the project MisionTIC2022 Ministry TIC - Caldas of University. Learn More

Basic Information

AGE:

ADDRESS:

camiloagdu@gmail.com / EMAIL: cristian.agudelo@ucaldas.edu.co

Manizales - Caldas - Colombia

29

PHONE: (+57) 314 860 6045

LANGUAGE: Spanish - English(A2)

Professional Skills

HTML	80%	CSS	40%
JAVASCRIPT	80%	PYTHON	80%
JAVA	75%	C#	70%
NODE.JS	55%	C#	70%
MYSQL	85%	POSTGRESQL	85%

Portfolio





Work Experience

JAN. 2022 - DEC. 2022 (CURRENT) **CALDAS UNIVERSITY**

Technological platform development engineer

Installation, configuration and customization of the DataSAE SIGA Moodle learning platforms for beneficiaries of the program MissionTIC2022 University of Caldas.

Development and deployment of Dashboard (Python, Djando, AWS) that helps decision making and early warnings.

Generation of SQL reports reported to the project manager.

JAN. 2021 - DEC 2021 **CALDAS UNIVERSITY**

TI project manager engineer

Lifting of requirements, analysis, development and deployment of IT projects proposed to the Vicerrectoria Proyección Universitaria Universidad de Caldas.

Management and operation of the digital platforms of the Vicerrectoría de Proyección Universitaria, integration of tools, management of profiles and content.

Perform technical support and QA of incidents on the website of the CCU and the VPU.

JUN. 2020 - DEC. 2020 PRACTICING

Caldas University

Design, develop, implement and display the page of the Centro Cultural Universitario Rogelio Salmona

Support for the creation and programming of user registration system and payment gateway for accreditations. Technical support and QA of incidents on the CCU website

JUN. 2019 - DEC. 2019 DEVMAN S.A.S -**DEVELOPMENT**

MANIZALES

Internship as Frontend developer

Development of new views for the virtual locker module of the Devman Logistics Cargo (DLC) system using the Angular programming language.

Education





References



tempus nascetur curabitur donec nam ullamcorper, laoreet nullam mauris dui aptent facilisis neque elementum ac, risus semper felis parturient fringilla rhoncus eleifend.

Habitasse venenatis commodo tempor eleifend arcu sociis sollicitudin ante pulvinar ad, est porta cras erat ullamcorper

volutpat metus duis platea convallis, tortor primis ac quisque etiam luctus nisl nullam fames. Ligula purus suscipit



